The voice of pressure once again pressed down on Fang Fei
Fang Fei collapsed on the ground
This time he really couldn't find any excuses.
Tears of regret and unwillingness flowed down uncontrollably
But in the world of cultivation
Tears are the most worthless thing
I can only coax those
Just a young boy entering the world for the first time
You guys here won't buy into his tricks.
I'm sorry I shouldn't have said that to you.
Please forgive me, Mu Xiaoshuai
False accusations can't do me any harm
It's not me you have to apologize to.
But everyone present
Haha sorry
Sorry, sorry.
I underestimated you too.
But you remember
Reputation is not everything
Strength is everything
Not enough talent for cultivation
You can only live at the bottom forever
And I
Soon I will be able to participate in the selection of core disciples.
That's the gap
My choice will never be wrong
You are right.
But you don't think
Should you pay more attention to your bestie now?
Lin Yue was a little surprised
Today, Mu Xiaoshuai's reaction every time
It was far beyond his expectations.
It's like a completely different person.
You're on your own.
Wait for Lin Yue to leave
The atmosphere here has finally returned to normal.
Haha bro
I jumped.
I've long disliked some people.
It seems like everyone has to indulge them.
Today I finally let out some steam
But this is only individual
Most of them are normal people
People were chatting away.
Soon, everyone was busy with their own things.
For true practitioners
This is just a small episode in life
But Mu Xiaoshuai keenly discovered
There are already some malicious eyes
Falling on oneself
Looks like I have to find a way to get home safely.
Sir, are you still going to continue?
The guy is all smiles
Mu Xiaoshuai's current work
It can be called a big customer.
This made him very happy
Because the larger the transaction amount,
The more commission you can get
Of course continue
My goal has not been achieved yet.
but
The transaction amount will be bigger and bigger in the future.
You need to prepare in advance
It's definitely okay.
If you are not sure
I'll go get our steward.
He has much more authority than I do.
That's troublesome.
The guy quickly walked into the back hall
A moment later
A middle-aged man in a purple robe
Came here with my friend.
Hello fellow Taoists
The middle-aged man smiled and greeted Mu Xiaoshuai
There is no difference in strength or age.
Take a higher stance
Shorter than Emperor Yuan
He is the manager of Jinyutang.
I heard Xiao Yan say
Something unpleasant happened here just now
It's Jinyutang's poor management.
I apologize to you
It's okay. It has nothing to do with you.
Let's talk about the deal first.
Fellow Daoist, a little faster
Then let's go to the back hall to talk.
I prepared some tea.
It's quieter there
Nayar
So the two of them walked to the back hall.